Hi.
My name is Daniel Baldwin.
I'm the general manager from Kurt's Auto Wrecking in American Fork, Utah.
And today we're giving you information on selling your junk car in Tampa.
Now the best thing you can do first of all is to clear your car out with all the stuff that you would like and take your license plates off.
Now next, there's many companies that you can sell your vehicle to.
In order to find those type of companies, you can get in the phone book and search, look under recycling centers or scrap yards or salvage yards.
Or, you can also go onto a web search like Google and type in any of those keywords again, and they will be able, and you'll pull up a bunch of scrap metal companies or recyclers, and they will be able to help you to find somewhere to sell those vehicles that are no longer operable or you just don't want anymore, and they're not worth a bunch of money.
Now, the best thing to do, again, is to have your title with you, and do not fill it out until you become on site so that we don't have any paperwork issues, and they're not any signatures in the wrong lines.
And you come in and we pay you cash at the time you drop it off.
We also tow them, so if it's very inoperable and, or you just don't want to drive it in, you can have us come in and we'll tow the vehicle, then you can bring later in that title and we pay at that time.